原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
我叫卡拉·佐·艾尔
My name is Kara Zor-El.
我来自氪星
I'm from Krypton.
我来到这颗星球避难
I'm a refugee on this planet.
翻译     DustD  洗七里  DerbyNinja
我被派往地球保护我的堂弟
I was sent to Earth to protect my cousin.
但我的太空舱被击中后偏离路线
But my pod got knocked off course.
在我到达地球之时
And by the time I got here,
翻译     阿p  左左  C·A
我的堂弟已经长大  成为了超人
my cousin had already grown up and become... Superman.
校对     肉松  饿得慌
我隐藏了我的真实身份
I hid who I really was
直到最近的一起事故
until one day when an accident
迫使我向世界揭示了自己的身份
forced me to reveal myself to the world.
时间轴    想念Gallifrey的Wholock  三水
对于大多数人  我只是凯特科全球媒体公司的记者
To most people, I'm a reporter at CatCo Worldwide Media.
后期     你是不是饿得慌
但私下里  我与收养家庭的姐姐一同为超查部工作
But in secret I work with my adopted sister at the DEO
保护这颗我称之为家园的星球
to protect this planet I call my home
总监     你是不是饿得慌
不受任何人的伤害
from anyone that means to cause it harm.
我是超女
I am Supergirl.
《超女》前情提要
‭Previously on Supergirl...
我得找到默茜和奥蒂斯·格雷夫斯
I need to find Mercy and Otis Graves.
他们曾在卡德摩斯工作
They worked for Cadmus.
我发过誓要过平静的生活
I made a vow ‭to live a peaceful life,
以另一种方式支持人们
stand up for people in a different way.
这是菲奥纳
This is Fiona.
她组织其他怪物
She's organizing other monsters
来对抗我们
to defend themselves against us.
"保卫外星人"  谁来保护我们
"Protect the aliens." Who's gonna protect us?
如果奥尔森先生继续扮演守护者一角
If Mr. Olsen were to resume his role as Guardian,
他将会被直接逮捕
he will be subject to immediate arrest.
十分感谢你们的帮助
Your assistance will be greatly noted.
地球第一
Earth first.
她还活着
Well, she's alive.
恢复意识只是早晚的问题
It's only a matter of time before she's conscious.
她很坚强
She's strong.
她在意志上也许很坚强
Emotionally maybe.
但她的脉搏很不稳定
But her pulse is erratic.
她病了
She's sick.
这件保护服还在过滤她体内的氪石
The suit is still filtering the Kryptonite out of her system.
在等她恢复的同时  我们做一些力所能及的事情
Well, then, we do what we can while we wait.
先从大气层着手
Starting with the atmosphere.
莉娜  我需要你和布莱尼去清理空气
Lena, I want you and Brainy to work on getting the air clean.
只有这样  我们才能让她从装甲里出来
It's the only way we're going to get her out of that thing.
好的
Will do.
如果你正在自己的思维殿堂里
If you're in your mind palace,
替我向花花问好
tell Streaky I said, "Hi."
我带了盾牌  我可以帮你找到默茜和奥蒂斯
I have my shield on me. I can help you find Mercy and Otis.
不行  如果你以守护者的身份出去  会被逮捕的
No. If you go out as Guardian, you'll be arrested.
她说得对  我们的人手已经够了
She's right. We already have enough boots on the ground.
-你还好吗  -我很不好
- Are you all right? - No, I am not.
你救了她的命  荣恩
Look, you saved her, J'onn.
她曾来找我帮她应对这件事  艾丽克斯
She came to me to help her fight this, Alex.
我拒绝了她
I turned her down.
我更想坚守自己不杀生的誓言
It was more important for me to keep my vow of non-violence
所以放弃了与卡拉并肩作战
than to fight by Kara's side.
你选择了尊重自己的新生活
You chose to honor a new path.
万一我做了错误的选择呢
What if I'm just making a big mistake?
我父亲是一位伟大的精神领袖
My father was ‭a great spiritual leader.
也许我永远也成不了他那样的人
Maybe I never will be.
也许我浪费了太长时间
Maybe I've just spent too many years
沉浸在愤怒之中  而没有做实质性的改变
steeped in rage to really change.
在我去救超女之前
You know, before I caught Supergirl,
我在市中心目睹了一场集会
I was downtown at a rally.
那是个反外星人团体
An anti-alien group.
里面全是极端分子  很可怕
Full of extremists. It was awful.
我差点...
I almost...
我朋友菲奥纳也失踪了
A friend of mine, Fiona, she's missing, too.
又一个外星人失踪了
Another alien. Missing.
就因为我选择了放下武器
Just because I chose to lay down arms.
我还把超查部的烂摊子扔给你来处理
And I left you here to pick up the pieces at the DEO.
你还好吗
How are you managing?
我很好
I'm good now.
听着
Look,
如果你真心想帮忙的话
if you really want to help,
可以用心灵感应来找他们
you can search ‭for them telepathically.
好
All right.
超查部沙漠分站
超 女
第四季 第四集
这是怎么回事
What's happening?
我怎么在这里面  放我出去
Why am I in here? Get me out!
没关系  深呼吸  有我在呢
Hey, it's okay. Just breathe. I'm here.
默茜向空中发射了氪石
Mercy fired Kryptonite into the air.
我没法呼吸  我没法呼吸
I can't breathe. I can't breathe.
别慌  看着我
No, no. Hey, look at me.
你没事的  这件保护服能维持你的生命
You're fine. This suit is keeping you alive.
深呼吸
Okay, so, just breathe.
我没事
I'm okay.
把事情的经过告诉我
Tell me everything.
这是干什么
What is this?
你们是谁
Who are you people?
放松  哥们  一切都是为了实现我们的目标
Relax, man. ‭Anything for the cause.
好了
Okay.
弄得逼真一点
Make it look convincing.
看起来肯定相当逼真
It's going to look real convincing.
我们不是不杀人类吗
I thought ‭we didn't kill humans.
他不是人类
He wasn't human.
而是我们的后患
He was loose ends.
我什么时候能把这个脱下来
When can I take this off?
等空气中彻底没有氪石的时候
When the air is 100% Kryptonite-free.
但我不能这样干坐着
But I can't just sit here.
这副装甲的能量
This armor has ‭the exact amount of energy
刚好够用来过滤你体内的氪石
to filter out the Kryptonite from your system.
如果你穿着它去战斗的话
If you use this to fight--
-可是...  -没有可是
- But-- - But nothing.
-我知道自己在做什么  -难道我不知道吗
- I know what I'm doing. - And I don't?
丹弗斯局长
Director Danvers.
我等会再来看你
I will check on you later.
B站点发生了意外
There's been an incident at Site B.
-什么意外  -是默茜·格雷夫斯干的
- What incident? - It's Mercy Graves, ma'am.
我们要马上赶过去
We need to get down there now.
他们已经跑了
They're already gone.
-伤亡人数是多少  -一人
- Casualties? - One.
另一名叛变的特工
Another agent who turned.
哥们  你挑错房子了
Man, you picked the wrong house.
我并不觉得啊
Don't think so.
像你这个年纪  独居
Man, your age lives alone.
找不到任何个人历史信息
No personal history to be found.
有点可疑  算是危险信号
A bit dodgy, that. Red flags.
告诉我  荣恩·荣兹
So, tell me, J'onn J'onzz,
你是怎么认识菲奥娜的
how do you know Fiona?
-你是她未婚夫  -是的
- You're her fiance. - That I am.
世界上最幸运的男人
Luckiest man in the world.
可是菲奥娜却失踪了
Only, Fiona dropped off the radar.
不像她的作风
Not like her.
你好像跟踪了她一段时间
And you seemed to have spent some time following her about.
-菲奥娜跟我只是朋友关系  -朋友
- Fiona's just a friend. - Well, friend,
我再问你一遍
I'll ask you once more.
她在哪儿
Where is she?
你今天最好不要惹我
Today is not the day to push me.
你不是地球人哦
Not from around here, are we?
放松  伙计  我没想伤害你
Relax, man. Weren't going to hurt you.
"你今天最好不要惹我"
"Today is not the day to push me."
我们是同一边的
We're on the same side.
-这是小菲的笔迹  -对  这是个警察编号
- This is Fi's handwriting. - Yeah, it's a badge number.
属于这个警察
And this is ‭the cop it belongs to.
菲奥娜之前在调查他
Fiona was looking into him.
我想接着追查  但被迫中止了
And I tried to follow up, but I got derailed.
-家里出了急事  -佩特赛利警官
- Family emergency. - Officer Petrocelli?
-很难接近他吗  -应该是的
- What, thorns in his garden? - I think so.
那我等不及要去会会他了
Then I am ‭just buzzing to meet him.
他有手段  你最好小心
He's got tricks. I'd be careful if I were you.
别担心  你有手段  我也有
Ah, don't worry. You've got tricks, I've got tricks, too.
你还没告诉我你叫什么名字
You got a name ‭to go with those tricks?
哦对  我真失礼
Right. How rude of me.
我是曼彻斯特·布莱克
I'm Manchester Black.
知道我们会怎么对付你们这种人吗
Do you know what we do to people like you?
早上好  克匹人和鱼蛉人
Good morning, Kopy and Hellgrammite.
当心  你要是碰了那玩意...
Careful. You so much as touch that thing...
那是什么
What is that?
是只寄生虫  像你们一样
It's a parasite. Like you.
戴着面具的懦夫竟然还会放狠话
Scary talk ‭from a coward in a mask.
"戴着面具的懦夫"
"Coward in a mask."
这副面具表示我的身份并不重要
This mask signifies that it doesn't matter who I am.
我是谁呢
Who am I?
我只是大局中的一小环
I'm just a small piece of something much bigger,
必不可少的一环
something necessary.
我会让地球重新拥有
Something that will restore this planet
正当的居民
to its rightful inhabitants.
稍等
Just a moment.
现在你们也是其中的一份子了
Now you're a part of it, too.
等我们离开这里之后...
When we get out of here...
各位  听好
All right, team, listen up.
你们可能也听说了
As you may have heard by now,
有两名特工叛变了
two of our agents have turned against us,
他们背叛了超查部的精神
against the very thing that this agency stands for,
那就是保护地球不遭受任何威胁
and that is to protect this planet from all threats.
无论是来自人类还是外星人的威胁
And that's from humans and aliens alike.
所以在任何时候  当你发现自己有所动摇
So, if at any point, you find yourself wavering,
我希望你们能停下来  环视四周
I want you to take a moment and look around
想想你们为什么要选择这份工作
and remember why you signed up.
我们会依靠彼此  正如以往一样
We'll lean on each other, like we always have.
我相信超查部
I believe in the DEO
因为我相信你们所有人
because I believe in every one of you.
我本想来喝啤酒  我觉得你选的酒更好
I came for a pint. I think you've got the better idea.
来杯跟他一样的
What he's having.
把整瓶都留下吧
Leave the bottle.
我今天被那群蟑螂抢了工作
Lost my job to one of those roaches today.
-抱歉  喝了几口就...  -没事没事
- Sorry. I get a few in me-- - No, no, no.
我最近经常听到这种话
I've been hearing that a lot lately.
-很恶心人  -没错
- It's disgusting. - It is.
敬咱们一杯
To us then.
我在努力  父亲
I'm trying, Father.
就像你教我的那样
Just like you taught me.
但我每次冥想  感受到的只有愤怒
But every time I reach out, all I feel is anger.
这让我很害怕  因为那愤怒来自我的内心
That scares me because the anger is all mine.
你说你会时刻伴我身旁
You said you'd be with me.
那就证明你所说的
So, prove it.
让我看到
Show me.
荣恩
J'onn.
菲奥纳
Fiona.
下一次呢
And the next one. Huh?
下一次集会是什么时候啊
The next rally, when might that be?
谁在乎
Who cares?
今晚才是真正的大戏
The real show is happening tonight.
哥伦比亚大街和第四大街  所有人都会去那里
Columbia and Fourth, that's where everyone is gonna go.
今晚会发生什么
What's happening tonight?
-不能告诉你  她会...  -她
- Can't tell you. She'd-- - She?
默茜  默茜
Mercy. Mercy--
美国人  根本不会喝酒
Americans, man. No idea how to drink.
你从他身上挖出什么了吗
Did you get anything from him?
他就一直在嘟囔"默茜"
Just kept whispering "Mercy."
你知道什么意思吗
It mean something to you?
默茜·格雷夫斯伤害了某个我在乎的人
Mercy Graves hurt somebody I care about.
我寻找过她  但...
I looked for her and...
我听到了菲奥娜的声音
I heard Fiona's voice.
我认为默茜可能抓了她做人质
I think Mercy may be holding her captive.
听到她  怎么听到的
Heard her? How?
我有心灵感应
I'm a telepath.
下回先把这么关键的信息告诉我
Let's lead with that next time.
我想菲奥娜在试图联系我
I think Fiona is trying to make contact with me.
他说他朋友们今晚要干大事
He said his mates had something nasty planned for tonight.
或许在那里我们能找到你说的默茜
Maybe that's where we can meet this Mercy of yours.
哥伦比亚大街和第四大街
Columbia and Fourth.
那边会发生什么
What's over there?
他们要去第四大道管区
They're going for the precinct on Fourth Street.
E小队  你们跟着我
Echo Team, I want you on me.
K小队  你们尾随我们做好掩护  咱们走
Kilo Team, you're behind us on overwatch. Let's go.
-我和你一起去  -绝不可能
- I'm coming with you. - The hell you are.
我可是穿着装甲呢
I'm literally wearing armor.
我也跟你说过  这副装甲的能量
And I told you that that armor is using
刚好够保证你的安全
everything it's got to keep you safe.
如果你再穿着它做别的...
If you do ‭anything else in it--
我之前也用一半的能力战斗过
I've fought ‭at half capacity before.
我能行的
I can do this.
这里有严格的指挥系统
There is ‭a chain of command here.
我了解我的能力  而且你需要我的帮助
I know what I'm capable of, and you need my help.
我需要的是你听从我的命令
What I need is for you to do exactly what I say.
-你好  -晚上好
- Howdy. - Evening.
你好
Howdy.
你刚才不是...
Weren't you just...
-你好  -你好
- Howdy. - Howdy.
抱歉  今天额外的警力我们包了
Sorry, we'll be providing the excessive force today.
跟打地鼠似的
It's a freaking Whac-A-Mole.
我告诉你别出来了
I told you to stay put!
你也知道我办不到
You know I can't do that.
超女
Supergirl!
布莱尼  我需要你马上赶过来
Brainy, I need you here now.
好了  起来吧
Right. Up you get.
我不会打你  但他会
I'm not gonna hit you, but he will.
-不杀生  -住手
- Ahimsa. - Stop!
是小菲
It's Fi.
荣恩
J'onn.
纳市警局防卫部门今晚遭到了外星人袭击
An alien attack this evening at NCPD Rampart Division,
有警官受伤
with reports of wounded officers.
我们获知超女穿着某种装甲出现在现场
We're told Supergirl was on the scene in some form of armor,
但是她似乎受了伤
but she appears injured
目前官方没有对她的情况做出回应
and there's no official word on her condition.
她没事
She's fine.
但再过三十秒
Thirty more seconds
她的保护服就会停止过滤氪辐射
and her suit would've stopped filtering K-radiation.
-她就会死  -死得惨烈
- And she would be dead. - Horribly so.
那是超女吗  还是蠢朋克的乐队成员
Is that Supergirl? Or one of the blokes from Daft Punk?
可惜是超女
Supergirl, unfortunately.
-你是曼彻斯特·布莱克  -听候吩咐
- Manchester Black, right? - At your service.
听说多亏有你事先提醒我们
I'm told you are the one to thank for the heads-up.
-关于她的事我很遗憾  -菲奥纳
- I'm sorry to hear about-- - Fiona.
是啊
Yeah.
你知道默茜和奥蒂斯为什么抓走她吗
Do you know why Mercy and Otis have her?
小菲有精神能力
Fi's a psychic.
我们认为他们要利用她控制其他外星人
We think they're using her to control the other aliens.
进行针对性打击制造恐慌
Targeted attacks to scare humans.
局长  总统在移动指挥部等你通话
Director, President on the line for you over in Mobile Command.
失陪
Excuse me.
哪位总统
President of what?
丹弗斯局长  我忍了你很多次了
Director Danvers, I have tolerated you
私有专利设备在你的监管下被盗
while a proprietary device was stolen on your watch,
你招募的特工叛变放走国家公敌
while a rogue agent you recruited set enemies of the state free.
我已尽我所能控制局面
And I've done everything possible to lock down the situation.
更有甚者  为你所有的无能"锦上添花"
And on top of that terrible Sunday of incompetence,
超女跑去进行"有趣的"自杀式任务
Supergirl goes on a fun suicide mission.
超女还活着  我们已经将她带回超查部
Supergirl is alive and we're taking her back to the DEO.
没有我的命令  超女不准离开超查部
Supergirl does not leave the DEO unless I give the order.
清楚了吗
Is that clear?
是的  先生
Yes, sir.
这个国家已经人人自危
The country is already nervous.
他们认为潜伏在白宫的外星人
They think an alien in the White House
暗地破坏了我们的民主
has undermined our democracy.
埋下了隐患
It's created a powder keg.
你的工作就是让公众感到安全
Your job is to make the public feel safe,
不是增加危机感
not more at risk.
处理好这件事  否则别怪我
So, handle this. Or so help me, I will have you-
就这样吧  局长
That will be all, Director.
过滤空气中的氪星石进展如何
Where are we with filtering the Kryptonite out of the air?
毫无进展
Nowhere.
我们在白费时间  因为我毫无成果
We're wasting our time because I've got nothing.
我们卡住了
We're sprocked!
最好的结果是超女的余生
The best case scenario is that Supergirl spends
都将被困在生命支持保护服里
the rest of her life confined in a life support suit.
当然  除非你一直藏着一个大吸尘器
Unless, of course, you've been hiding some sort of giant vacuum
能吸走大气层里的每一个氪石粒子
that can suck every particle of Kryptonite out of the atmosphere.
好吧
Okay. Wha...
等等  你哭了吗
Wait, are you crying?
没有
No.
真没想到
That's unanticipated.
怎么
What?
我不是机器人
I'm not a robot.
我是科技有机体  我有感情
I'm techno-organic. I have feelings.
你也该哭
You should be crying, too.
-这是逻辑的眼泪  -我是过来人
- These are tears of logic. - Listen, I've been where you are now,
相信我  我也有感情
and believe you me, I have feelings.
现在我感到十分愤怒
Right now, I'm feeling intense rage.
我创造这个设备是为了行善  拯救地球
I created this device for good. To save Earth.
可又一次  我的科技被偷走滥用
And once again, my technologies have been stolen and abused.
现在我简直气得想杀人
I could murder someone right now.
人类总能感到这种感觉吗
Do humans feel like this all the time?
很想搞破坏的感觉
It's intense and disruptive.
你们怎么还能去完成任何事
How do you get anything done?
我的解决方式吗
My solution?
-盒子  -盒子
- Boxes. - Boxes.
好  哪种  纸盒  木盒  树脂盒
Yes. What variety? Cardboard? Wooden? Lucite?
想象出来的盒子
Imaginary.
我想让你想象你有很多小小的盒子
I want you to imagine that you're full of tiny, itty-bitty boxes.
然后你整理你的感情
And then I want you to take your feelings
塞进那些小小的盒子里
and I want you to shove them into those itty-bitty boxes.
然后把那些小盒子深深埋进内心
And then I want you to take those and shove them way deep down
直到你忘记自己最初有感情
till you forget you even had feelings in the first place.
然后你和我搞科研
Then you and I are gonna do science
把空气过滤干净  明白了吗
and get this air cleaned, understand?
好
Okay.
我照做了
I've done it.
我感觉好多了
I feel much better.
很好
Excellent.
事实上  我想到了
Actually, I figured it out.
是纳米机器人
It's nanites.
L公司有纳米技术开发部门吧
L-Corp owns a nano-tech subdivision, yes?
以前是斯菲瑞科实业公司
Formerly ‭Spheerical Industries.
我们只要改写纳米机器人的程序
We just have to reprogram the nanites
机器人就能检测并从大气中滤除氪石
so that they can detect and filter the Kryptonite out of the atmosphere.
我们就不需要巨型吸尘器了
We don't need ‭a giant vacuum cleaner.
只是数以亿计的小个体而已
Just trillions of small ones.
我和你说过不要离开小屋
I told you ‭not to leave the premises.
我救了一个人
I saved someone's life.
但你是在拿自己的生命冒险
By jeopardizing your own.
我是英雄  艾丽克斯  我愿意冒险
I'm a hero, Alex. I take risks.
你也是超查部的员工
You are also an employee of the DEO.
我们同事了好几年
We've been working together for years.
为什么突然间变成这样
Why are you all of a sudden acting like this?
因为我现在是局长
Because I am the director now!
如果有人受伤  我要负责
If someone gets hurt, that's on me.
如果有人逃出去
And if someone escapes
在空气中散播氪石
and fills the air with Kryptonite,
我也要负责
that's on me!
如果你死了...
And if you had died--
但我没死
But I didn't die.
要是你
And if it were you,
也会这么做的
you would have done the exact same thing.
我会仍然以自己的判断行事
I am not going to stop using my own judgement.
制度是合理的
We have rules for a reason.
不然这个地方就会四分五裂
Otherwise this place would fall apart.
如果你想继续和我同事
So, if you want to ‭continue working with me,
那就得服从命令
then you will obey orders.
这是我作为你的指挥官
And as your commanding officer,
最后一次警告你
this is your final warning.
我好像记得
I seem to recall
你告诉我超女死了
you telling me ‭that Supergirl was dead.
我们没说过这是正式确认的事
We never said it was official.
我们会杀死她的
We'll make her dead.
计划照常进行
The plan still stands.
你的计划太渺小了
Your plan is small.
你说什么
Excuse me?
你想让人们看到外星人是怪物
You want to show people that aliens are monsters.
很好  但是攻击保护他们的人
That's good, but you don't do that
攻击警察和超查部的人是没用的
by attacking their protectors, the police, the DEO.
那样会让他们感到害怕
Yeah, that will make them afraid.
让他们心里产生恐惧
That'll make them feel fear, up here, in their mind.
要让他们感受到切身之痛才行
What you need to do is make them feel it in their bones.
那...
And how
你打算如何达到这一目的
do you plan on doing that exactly?
让他们知道
You show them
他们担心自己的孩子
that they need to be afraid for their children.
先别管外星人
All right, forget the aliens.
我们要找这个女人  菲奥纳·伯恩
We're looking for this woman, Fiona Byrne.
找到她  就能找到所有人
We find her, we find them all.
汇报情况
Sitrep.
我和莉娜想到办法
Lena and I have found a way
清除大气层中的氪石了
to clear the atmosphere of Kryptonite.
-我们重新配置了L公司  -要多久
- We've reconfigured L-Corp-- - Okay, how long?
不清楚  纳米机器人以前从未吞食过氪石
Uncertain. None of the nanites have eaten Kryptonite before
它们当然会很紧张
and they're understandably very nervous.
别要求太高  毕竟它们只是纳米机器人
I don't wanna ask too much of them, they're just nanites.
"不杀生"来自印度语吗
That word, "Ahimsa," it's Hindu?
意思是不杀生
It means non-violence.
只是小菲常说的一个词
Just something Fi used to say.
跟我说说她
Tell me about her.
我遇到小菲的时候  我
When I met Fi, I was...
你可能会称之为"拉帮结派"
Well, I guess you'd call it "ganged up."
球迷大火拼
It was football hooligans.
抱歉  足球迷大火拼
Sorry, soccer hooligans.
打架的借口
Any excuse to break a window.
我爸是我们的老板
We worked for my dad.
他教我如何在斗争中获胜
He taught me how to win a fight.
只要掌握了窍门就很简单
It's easy, ‭once you know the trick.
大脑有个开关
There's a switch in here.
阻止你伤害他人
Keeps you from hurting another person.
你可以打开
You can turn it on...
再关闭
And off.
那你为什么收手了
So, why did you stop?
我遇到了小菲
I met Fi.
她是帮我们帮派记账的
She kept the books for the gang.
没有伤害任何人
Didn't hurt no one.
除了我  因为她只看了我一眼
No one but me, ‭because one look from her,
我就死了  真的
and I was‭ dead, man.
死心塌地追随她
Gone, hers.
然后她教会了我
And she showed me...
教会了我其他方式
Showed me other ways.
不使用暴力的方式
Non-violent ways.
不杀生
Ahimsa.
后来成员们发现她是外星人
Then the boys found out she was an alien.
于是那里就不安全了  于是我让她...
Wasn't safe there anymore. So, I told her...
我让她来美国  这里比较安全
I told her to go to the States so she'd be safe.
等等
Wait a minute.
那枚戒指
That ring...
我见过一个类似的
I saw something like this.
只有那么一瞬间  后来我听到了菲奥纳的声音
Just a fragment, right before I heard Fiona's voice.
对  两个戒指是一对
Yeah, she has a matching one.
我就需要这个
This is what I need.
一个护身符
A talisman.
她随身携带的  拥有情感关联的东西
Something on her person with emotional weight.
它可以作为信号塔  加强我和她的联系
I can use it like a cell tower to amplify my link with her.
奥尔森先生
Mr. Olsen.
-一切还好吗  -当然  我只是...
- Everything okay? - Of course, yeah. Um...
我只是想来表达一下感谢
I just wanted to mention how thankful I am.
我最近在读格兰特的一些事迹
'Cause, uh, I've been reading about Ms. Grant,
还有凯特科和你
and CatCo, and you.
你知道我们的工作是很重要的吧
You know what we do up here is important, right?
我也在读一些法律事务
I've also been reading about matters of the law.
你是否知道如果一个人
Did you know someone could be prosecuted
反复犯同一罪行  可能会被起诉
for continued instances of the same crime?
知道
Yeah.
-我有律师  -当然
- I have a lawyer. - Of course.
我并不是说  你在考虑
I'm not even saying you're thinking
再次拿起盾牌
of taking up the shield again.
但如果你在考虑
But, if you were,
尤其是现在超女倒下了  请不要那样做
especially with ‭Supergirl down... Don't.
你还是之前的尼娅·纳尔吗  那位新记者
Is this the same Nia Nal I'm talking to, the cub reporter
她自信而正当地说服了她的老板
who convincingly and rightfully convinced her boss
采取行动
to act?
在无辜的人遭到攻击时挺身而出
And to speak out when the innocent are being attacked?
是啊  这不像是我能说出来的话
I know. I don't sound like myself.
但那是因为这次不一样
But that's ‭because this is different.
如果你再次出手
If you go out there again,
我觉得会发生危险
I have a feeling ‭something bad will happen.
可是英雄
Heroes go out there,
即便知道会发生危险  他们也会出手
even when they know something bad's gonna happen.
所以他们才是英雄
That's what makes them heroes.
-有效果了  -切斯
- It's working. - 'Ches.
小菲
Fi?
她能听到我说话吗
Can she hear me?
又见面了  亲爱的
Here you are, darling.
你看起来真不错
You look an absolute state.
你看起来也很美
And you look perfect.
他们伤害你了吗
Did they hurt you?
没什么我承受不了的
Nothing I can't handle.
是你第一个发现的
You were the first person to see this.
你怎么能不参与进来呢
How can you not join me now?
因为这不再是我的战役
Because it's no longer in my path to fight.
抱歉  我不能陪你去战斗
I'm sorry, I cannot join your battle.
怎么回事
What's happening?
我们得尽快行动
We need to move quick.
菲奥娜  你知道自己在哪里吗
Fiona, do you know where you are?
我不知道  他们用寄生物控制了我的心灵感应
I don't. They're using a parasite to control my telepathy powers
以此来控制其他外星人
to control other aliens.
我觉得他们好像把我放在了人群附近
I think they've got me near some sort of a crowd.
我能闻到蛋糕和甜点的味道
I can smell cakes and sweets.
有点像糖果店  还有音乐
Like the pick 'n' mix. And there's music.
-让她回来  -我做不到
- Bring her back. - I can't.
-为什么不行  -我做不到
- Why not? - I can't!
我尽力了  艾丽克斯
I tried, Alex.
我试过祷告  用我思想的力量
I tried to use prayer, the power of my mind
找到菲奥娜  但是
to find Fiona, but...
每当我觉得找到线索的时候
Every time I think I'm getting somewhere,
就会被愤怒打断
my mind is ‭just hijacked with anger.
还有暴力  以及我让卡拉失望了
Violence, how I failed Kara.
没用的  我辜负了我父亲的期望
It's no use, I'm not the man my father hoped I'd be.
我唯一做对的事  就是让你接管超查部
Only thing I've done right is put you in charge of the DEO.
不  这...
No, that's...
这是你唯一做错的事
That's the only thing that you've done wrong.
什么
What?
一切都是我的错
Everything is my fault.
这一切...都怪我  不是吗
I mean, all of this, it's... It's on me, okay?
以前我眼皮底下发生了很多坏事
A lot of bad things happened here under my watch.
但我之所以取胜是我相信了直觉
But I prevailed ‭because I trusted my gut,
和我的战友
and my people.
艾丽克斯  你要相信自己的直觉
Alex, you have to trust your gut.
这么做  你就能成功
You do that and you will soar.
你知道吗  你身上...
You realize that, um, wisdom
散发着智慧
literally emanates from you?
你现在正是你父亲所期望的那样
You are exactly who your father saw you would be.
我们如何协调理想与现实中的自己  艾丽克斯
How do we reconcile who we are with who we wanna be, Alex?
原谅自己
We forgive ourselves.
和平并不意味着不作为
Pacifism doesn't mean inaction.
它只是意味着你必须学会
It just means that you have to learn how to fight
如何不拿起武器而战斗
without raising the sword.
我让你接管是对的
I was right to put you in charge.
话说得太早了
Oh, that was too soon.
把你看到的都告诉我  好吗
Okay, so, you tell me everything that you saw. Okay?
我们要找到菲奥纳和带走她的人
We're gonna find Fiona and the people who took her.
是  老大
Yes, boss.
我正在搜寻纳欣诺市一百英里内
I'm scanning for anything that draws a crowd
任何吸引人群的活动
within 100 miles of National City.
并把活动上每一种从自选小店买的食物
Cross-referencing those events with every item of food sold
和所有已知的通灵标志进行交叉对比
at a pick 'n' mix and every known ‭psychic energy signature.
那你找到了吗
So, have you found them?
当然找到了  在纳欣诺市游乐场
Yes, of course. They're at the National City Fair.
我去找曼彻斯特  干得漂亮  布莱尼亚克
I'll go get Manchester. Nice work, Brainiac.
组织突击队  有空的特工都上
Okay, ‭assemble a strike team, all available agents.
确保五分钟内准备就绪
And make sure ‭that they're ready to go in five minutes.
是  长官
Yes, ma'am.
假设...
Hypothetically,
没有超女  我们有多少胜算
what are the odds of us winning without Supergirl?
外星人受到精神控制
Aliens being mind-controlled,
失去了保护自己的本能
with no instinct to protect themselves.
只能伤害别人
Only harm others.
胜算不大
The odds are not great.
那有了她呢
And with her?
她出手就能赢
If she can handle the fight, you will win.
但大气里还有氪石
But the atmosphere isn't clear of Kryptonite.
那就赶快清除干净
Then finish getting it clear.
-你得上战场了  -什么
- You've been drafted. - Wait, what?
空气里不是还有氪石吗
Isn't there still Kryptonite in the air?
我以为你是按规矩行事的
I thought you were ‭doing things by the book.
那是之前
I was.
但我真的需要你去帮我
But I really need you out there with me.
我之前很害怕
I was scared.
害怕失败  让大家失望
Of failing, of letting everybody down.
总统  整个国家
The president, the country.
所以我觉得
So, I thought
规矩能防止我把事情搞砸
the rules would protect me from screwing everything up.
丹弗斯姐妹向来不看重规矩
Danvers sisters have never really been big on rules.
我知道  只是暂时忘了
I know and I forgot that for a minute.
对不起
I'm sorry.
打赢这场战的唯一办法
The only way that we're gonna win this thing,
就是相信你我的直觉
is if I trust my instincts and I trust yours.
你说的对
And you're right.
空气里的氪石没清完
The air isn't fully clear.
所以这是一场冒险
So, this is a risk.
你觉得自己能行吗
Do you think you can do it?
我能
I know I can.
那就穿上战服吧
Then suit up.
遵命
No choice.
纳欣诺市游乐场
你踩坏了我的碧波
You smashed my Beebo.
人生就是这样的
That's a metaphor for life.
你能别再招人注意了吗
Will you stop drawing attention to yourself?
我们是来干活的
We have a job to do.
-情况怎么样  -外星人被精神控制了
- How are we doing? - Aliens are mind-controlled.
这边没问题
So all good here.
纳欣诺市游乐场发生了袭击
Reported attack at the National City Fair.
警察封锁现场
Police are on-scene securing the area,
建议人们不要靠近游乐场
and people are being advised to stay clear of the fairgrounds.
今天早些时候人们聚集
The attack began earlier today
在游乐场时发生了袭击
as people packed the fairgrounds...
空气质量百分之七十五
Air quality at 75%.
放开她
Drop her.
别毁了派
Not the pies.
我不敢相信他去了
I can't believe he went.
有小盒子
Little boxes.
-空气质量如何  -百分之九十
- Air check? ‭- Ninety percent.
如果保护服脱落还是致命的
That's still lethal if the suit fails.
你得撤回去  你得保存实力
You need to back off. You need to try and conserve.
我需要再处理一件事
I've just gotta handle one more thing.
在那里
Over there.
各位  各位  我们得走了
Guys? Guys, we gotta go.
各位
Guys?
发生了什么
What's happening?
保护服受到了太多伤害
The suit's taking too much damage.
所以  能量只能用于维持生命
So, power's being diverted to life support.
我来给你充能
I'll give you a jump.
你要稳住
You're gonna wanna hold still.
谢谢充能
Thanks for the charge.
现在怎么了
What's happening now?
我这边显示系统全面瘫痪了
I'm reading full systems failure.
保护服被锁定了  我动不了
The suit's locking down. I can't move.
我们得走了  姐
We should leave, sis.
我们达成原来的目的才能走
Not till we finish what we started.
让她死  了解了
Make her dead, got it.
该死的
Screw it.
我管这个叫"开瓶器"
I call this move "The can opener."
空气里还残留着氪石  对吧
Ah, there's still Kryptonite in the air, right?
所以  我扣下扳机会发生什么呢
So, uh, what happens if I pull the trigger?
-不  停下  -空气质量检查
- No, stop! - Air check.
空气百分之九十九纯净
The atmosphere is 99% clear.
你为什么要保护她
Why are you protecting her?
你为什么要保护他们
Why are you protecting any of them?
-看看他们在做什么  -不是他们在做这些
- Look at what they do. - They aren't doing this.
-你才是罪魁祸首  -人们需要恐惧
- You are. - People need to be afraid.
哪怕是我们得硬塞给他们
Even if it means we have to sell it to them.
百分百纯净
100%.
无需给生命维持系统提供能量了
Rerouting power away from life support.
立即解锁保护服
Unlocking suit now.
对  她说得没错
Yeah, what she said.
欢迎来到奥蒂斯
Welcome to Otis-- Oh.
不  我们为自由而战
No! We're fighting for freedom.
为了干掉小强
For roaches.
为了
For...
默茜
Mercy!
现在他们自由了
Now, they're free.
小菲
Fi?
我来了  亲爱的  我来了
Hey, I'm here, love. I'm here.
我来了  我来了
I'm here, I'm here.
你来了  亲爱的
Here you are, darling.
好的  我们得送她去医院
Okay, okay. We need to get her to a hospital.
我为你坚持了下来
I held on for you.
我知道  亲爱的  但是一定还能做些什么
I know, love. But there has to be something we can do.
我们一定还能做些什么
There has to be something we can do.
-我可以带走她的伤痛  -动手啊
- I could take away her pain. - Then do it!
拜托了  伙计
Please, man.
我在这  我在这
I'm here, I'm here.
答应我
Just promise me...
不  停下
No, stop it.
-答应我  -不
- Promise me. - No.
请不要生气
Please don't be angry.
我知道你会生气的
I know you'll want to.
我爱你  曼彻斯特
I love you, Manchester.
我爱你
I love you.
我不想要你离开我
I don't want you to leave me.
我会照顾好你的  我保证我会照顾好你的
I'll look after you. I promise I'll look after you.
不愧是我的女人
That's my girl.
小菲
Fi?
为什么是我
Why me, man?
他们夺走了我的宝贝
They took my baby.
They took my baby, man.
为什么  为什么
Why, man? Why, man?
我知道十有八九
I know that in all likelihood,
你会直接重新投入工作
you'll want to jump right back into work.
但是呢
But?
但是...
But...
这是怎么回事
What's going on?
祝贺你  丹弗斯局长
Congratulations, Director Danvers.
好了  我们终于打了一场胜仗
All right, we put one in the win column.
这是你们大家的功劳
And that's... That's because of you.
你们都应该感到自豪
You all should be so proud of yourselves.
-您有何贵干  -你好  我是劳伦·哈雷上校
- May I help you? - Hi. I'm Colonel Lauren Haley.
-您好  -美国总统派我来的
- Hi. - POTUS sent me.
鉴于你违背了直接命令
Given how you disobeyed direct orders,
他认为你需要有人监督
he thought you might need some oversight.
您会在这里待多久  上校
And how long will you be with us, Colonel?
需要多久就待多久
As long as it takes.
你应该提前跟我商量一下
It just should've been a discussion.
你指望我怎么做  坐视不管吗
What did you expect me to do, just sit here?
万一你被捕入狱怎么办
What if you'd been sent to prison?
关于这件事  我跟律师谈过了
Yeah, about that. I talked to my lawyer.
奇怪的是  我没有遭到新的控告
It's weird. I... No new charges.
没收到起诉书
No indictment.
警察甚至还会授权守护者作为警方代表
The cops might even deputize Guardian.
我知道
I know, it's, uh...
我做梦都想不到会有这么好的结局
It worked out better than I could have possibly imagined.
-姑娘  什么事  -你成了热点人物
- Hey, kid, what's up? - You're trending.
是吗
Yeah?
詹姆斯·奥尔森  人类英雄
情况不妙
In a bad way.
《守护者踩死蟑螂》  什么
"Roaches crushed ‭by Guardian's boot." What?
《人类奋起反击》
"Humans strike back strong."
《自由守护者》
"Guardian of Liberty."
太棒了
Yes.
我正需要吃点甜食
Mmm, I really need those.
-你买了...  -大黄派吗  买了三个
- Do you have any, um-- - Rhubarb? Yeah, three.
你以为我是业余的吗
What do you think this is, amateur hour?
你是馅饼女王
The queen of pies.
谢谢
Thank you.
你还好吗
Hey, you okay?
比起我以前的经历  被女大兵监督工作不算什么
Oh, I've dealt with much worse than G.I. Jane coming to babysit me.
可是如果我听了你的话  她就不会被派来了
Yeah, but she wouldn't be here if I had followed your orders.
你六个小时前怎么不拿出这种态度呢
I'm sorry, where was this attitude six hours ago?
对不起
I'm sorry.
你跟从了自己的直觉
You followed your instincts.
我也一样  所以不必道歉
And I followed mine, so there's no apologies.
身为领导  就该完成该做的工作
Being a leader means doing what needs to get done
然后承受后果
and taking the consequences.
所以  我们做得对
So, we did the right thing.
无论遇到任何困难
Well, hell or high water,
我都会做你的后盾
I've got your back.
无论遇到任何困难
Hell or high water.
说起困难  你能帮我挠挠后背吗
Oh, speaking of, can you please scratch this one spot...
-绝对不行  -我之前可是穿了全身装甲
- Oh, absolutely not. - I was in a full body cast.
-我知道  -我够不到  都快痒死了
- I know. - I can't... It's really bothering me.
-不行  -这...
- No. - It's...
全买下来多少钱
How much for the lot?
空气中的氪石
清理干净了
我能继续训练了吗
他们死了
They're dead.
默茜和奥蒂斯
Mercy and Otis.
超女回来了
Supergirl is back.
我们该怎么办啊
What are we supposed to do?
住嘴  别说了
Stop! Stop. Stop.
我告诉过你  没有"我们"这回事
What did I tell you? There is no "we."
我们是谁并不重要
It doesn't matter who we are.
谁来领导我们也不重要
It doesn't matter who leads us.
詹森  唯一重要的是
Jensen, the only thing that matters is that
你加入进来是有原因的  对吧
you joined up for a reason. Right?
原因就是你想有所成就  对吧
And that reason is because you wanted to make something of yourself. Right?
-对  -好的
- Yeah. -Okay.
那我们就看看能把你变成什么样
Let's see what we can make.
好
Okay.